Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Antarctica [includes color photographs], 1962 November - December; 16 (Box 1537)
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30106-11-62; 20 November 1962; A picture donated by the National Geographic Society is carried to New Byrd Station, Antarctica by (L to R) Dr. James Mooney, Deputy Antarctic Projects Officer, Mr. Lowell Thomas, renown American radio and news commentator, and the U. S. Secretary of Commerce the Hon. [Honorable] Luther H. Hodges. Secretary Hodges presents the picture at New Byrd Station. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC) F. Kazukaitis, USN., 14-verso
    - [6 copies] 20 Nov 1962; General James E. Doolittle (left) and explorer-news commentator Lowell Thomas (right) greet two of the Antarctic support activities men who wintered over at South Pole Station during DEEPFREEZE 62. Next to General Doolittle is Claud Craig, RMCA, USN; to his left is Harold D. Crain, UT1, USN. Both Craig and Crain were guests of Commander, Antarctic Support Activities at a midnight buffet supper for the DEEPFREEZE 62 Pole winter over men at the McMurdo Station mess hall at which General Doolittle and Mr. Thomas were present., 15
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30114-11-62; 20 Nov 1962; General James E. Doolittle (left) and explorer-news commentator Lowell Thomas (right) greet two of the Antarctic support activities men who wintered over at South Pole Station during DEEPFREEZE 62. Next to General Doolittle is Claud Craig, RMCA, USN; to his left is Harold D. Crain, UT1, USN. Both Craig and Crain were guests of Commander, Antarctic Support Activities at a midnight buffet supper for the DEEPFREEZE 62 Pole winter over men at the McMurdo Station mess hall at which General Doolittle and Mr. Thomas were present. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Third Class (PH3) Philip T. McClure, USN, 15-verso
    - 22 November 1962, Congressman Poage of Texas, and Lowell Thomas, renown radio news commentator, partake of traditional Thanksgiving dinner at the enlisted men's chow hall at Advance Headquarters for Operations Deep Freeze at Harewood Christchurch, New Zealand. They arrived at Harewood International Airport Thursday morning after completing an inspection tour of U. S. scientific bases in the Antarctic., 16
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30061-11-62; 22 November 1962, Congressman Poage of Texas, and Lowell Thomas, renown radio news commentator, partake of traditional Thanksgiving dinner at the enlisted men's chow hall at Advance Headquarters for Operations Deep Freeze at Harewood Christchurch, New Zealand. They arrived at Harewood International Airport Thursday morning after completing an inspection tour of U. S. scientific bases in the Antarctic. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate First Class (PH1) Marco J. Billante, USN., 16-verso
    - 22 November 1962; Among the visiting dignitaries who arrived from an inspection tour of the U. S. scientific bases in the Antarctic on Thursday morning in time for Thanksgiving dinner at Harewood were the Honorable Luther H. Hodges, U. S. Secretary of Commerce, and Lowell Thomas, renown radio news commentator., 17
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30062-11-62; 22 November 1962; Among the visiting dignitaries who arrived from an inspection tour of the U. S. scientific bases in the Antarctic on Thursday morning in time for Thanksgiving dinner at Harewood were the Honorable Luther H. Hodges, U. S. Secretary of Commerce, and Lowell Thomas, renown radio news commentator. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate First Class (PH1) Marco J. Billante, USN, 17-verso
    - 22 November 1962; U. S. Secretary of Commerce, the Honorable Luther H. Hodges (center), and Lowell Thomas, renown radio news commentator, at the salad bar in the enlisted men's chow hall at Advanced Headquarters of Operation Deep Freeze at Harewood, Christchurch, New Zealand. They arrived at Harewood International Airport Thursday morning after an inspection tour of U. S. scientific bases in the Antarctic., 18
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-30053-11-62; 22 November 1962; U. S. Secretary of Commerce, the Honorable Luther H. Hodges (center), and Lowell Thomas, renown radio news commentator, at the salad bar in the enlisted men's chow hall at Advanced Headquarters of Operation Deep Freeze at Harewood, Christchurch, New Zealand. They arrived at Harewood International Airport Thursday morning after an inspection tour of U. S. scientific bases in the Antarctic. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate First Class (PH1) Marco J. Billante, USN., 18-verso
    - 31 December 1962; An Adelie penguin with her baby chick at Cape Crozier, Antarctica. Adelies are the clowns of the Antarctic and often offer some unusual entertainment to the men of "Deep Freeze." Since they have no fear of humans, they sometimes get in the way of men trying to build bases and operate equipment., 19
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAM-31622-12-62; 31 December 1962; An Adelie penguin with her baby chick at Cape Crozier, Antarctica. Adelies are the clowns of the Antarctic and often offer some unusual entertainment to the men of "Deep Freeze." Since they have no fear of humans, they sometimes get in the way of men trying to build bases and operate equipment. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph by Photographer's Mate Second Class (PH2) Thomas J. Regina, USN, 19-verso
    - 31 December 1962, An Adelie penguin with her baby chick at Cape Crozier, Antarctica., 20
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAM-31622-12-62; 31 December 1962, An Adelie penguin with her baby chick at Cape Crozier, Antarctica. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Second Class (PH2) Thomas J. Regina, USN, 20-verso
    - 31 December 1962, An Adelie penguin at Cape Crozier, Antarctica., 21
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAM-31622-12-62; 31 December 1962, An Adelie penguin at Cape Crozier, Antarctica. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Second Class (PH2) Thomas J. Regina, USN, 21-verso
    - 31 December 1962, A group of Adelie penguin at Cape Crozier, Antarctica., 22
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAM-31622-12-62; 31 December 1962, A group of Adelie penguin at Cape Crozier, Antarctica. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Second Class (PH2) Thomas J. Regina, USN, 22-verso
    - [2 copies] L.T. in hat and parka, 23
  - Subject files: Antarctica, 1963 September - 1965; 17 (Box 1537)
    - 30 November 1963; Capetown, South Africa---crews of both C-130's shortly before departure on historic non-stop flight from Capetown, to McMurdo Sound, Antarctica. L/R front row, LCDR. [Lieutenant Commander] R. G. Dickerson (Plane Commander of lead plane) RADM. [Rear Admiral] James R. Reedy, CDR. [Commander] G. R. Kelly USN, Commanding Officer VX-6, LCDR. Lieutenant Commander] W. B. Kulak, Plane Commander of second plane., 1
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-40009-9-63; 30 November 1963; Capetown, South Africa---crews of both C-130's shortly before departure on historic non-stop flight from Capetown, to McMurdo Sound, Antarctica. L/R front row, LCDR. [Lieutenant Commander] R. G. Dickerson (Plane Commander of lead plane) RADM. [Rear Admiral] James R. Reedy, CDR. [Commander] G. R. Kelly USN, Commanding Officer VX-6, LCDR. Lieutenant Commander] W. B. Kulak, Plane Commander of second plane. Credit line to read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Lt. JG [Lieutenant, Junior Grade] H. S. Hemphill USN, 1-verso
    - [2 copies] 1 October 1963; LCDR. [Lieutenant Commander] R. G. Dickerson, Plane Commander of the lead LC-130F #148318, during their historic non-stop flight from Capetown, South Africa to McMurdo Sound, Antarctica, a distance of more than 4,000 miles. Credit line to read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Lt. JG [Lieutenant, Junior Grade] H. S. Hemphill USN, 2
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-40023-10-63; 1 October 1963; LCDR. [Lieutenant Commander] R. G. Dickerson, Plane Commander of the lead LC-130F #148318, during their historic non-stop flight from Capetown, South Africa to McMurdo Sound, Antarctica, a distance of more than 4,000 miles. Credit line to read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Lt. JG [Lieutenant, Junior Grade] H. S. Hemphill USN, 2-verso
    - 1 October 1963, CDR. [Commander] George R. Kelly, Commanding Officer of AIRDEVRON SIX at the controls of LC-130F #148318 during the historic non-stop flight from Capetown, South Africa to McMurdo Sound, Antarctica, a distance of 4,000 miles., 3
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-40024-10-63; 1 October 1963, CDR. [Commander] George R. Kelly, Commanding Officer of AIRDEVRON SIX at the controls of LC-130F #148318 during the historic non-stop flight from Capetown, South Africa to McMurdo Sound, Antarctica, a distance of 4,000 miles. Credit line to read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Lt. (JG) [Lieutenant, Junior Grade] H. S. Hemphill USN, 3-verso
    - 1 October 1963, L to R: LCDR [Lieutenant Commander] W. B. Kurlak, Plane Commander of LC-130F #148320; LCDR [Lieutenant Commander] R. G. Dickerson, Plane Commander of LC-130F #148318; RADM [Rear Admiral] James R. Reedy, Commander Task Force 43; CDR [Commander] George R. Kelly, Commanding Officer of AIRDEVRON SIX: At McMurdo Sound, Antarctica on completion of their historic non-stop flight from Capetown, South Africa to McMurdo., 4
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three, XAC-40025-10-63; 1 October 1963, L to R: LCDR [Lieutenant Commander] W. B. Kurlak, Plane Commander of LC-130F #148320; LCDR [Lieutenant Commander] R. G. Dickerson, Plane Commander of LC-130F #148318; RADM [Rear Admiral] James R. Reedy, Commander Task Force 43; CDR [Commander] George R. Kelly, Commanding Officer of AIRDEVRON SIX: At McMurdo Sound, Antarctica on completion of their historic non-stop flight from Capetown, South Africa to McMurdo. Credit line to read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Lt. (JG) [Lieutenant, Junior Grade] H. S. Hemphill USN, 4-verso
    - 3 October 1963; RADM [Rear Admiral] James R. Reedy USN, Commander of OPERATION DEEPFREEZE and Lowell Thomas (left) CBS News Correspondent after completing an unprecedented non-stop flight from Capetown, South Africa to McMurdo Station Antarctic terminating at Harewood International Airport, Christchurch, New Zealand., 5
    - Task Force Forty Three, XAC 40,015-10-63; 3 October 1963; RADM [Rear Admiral] James R. Reedy USN, Commander of OPERATION DEEPFREEZE and Lowell Thomas (left) CBS News Correspondent after completing an unprecedented non-stop flight from Capetown, South Africa to McMurdo Station Antarctic terminating at Harewood International Airport, Christchurch, New Zealand. Credit line should read "Official U.S. Navy Photograph" by Photographer's Mate Chief (PHC) Frank Kazukaitis, USN, 5-verso
    - Date 10-3-1963, Photographer Kazukaitis, PHC, USN; Subject: RADM [Rear Admiral] James R. Reedy, USN, Commander of OPERATION DEEPFREEZE and Lowell Thomas, CBS News Correspondent hold a press conference with the New Zealand press media in Christchurch after completing an unprecedented non-stop flight from Capetown, South Africa to McMurdo Sound Antarctica, terminating at Harewood International Airport, Christchurch New Zealand. RADM Reedy attended the World Conference of the Scientific Committee of Antarctica Research (SCAR) held in Capetown, South Africa, 6
    - Verso: USN 825946, Date 10-3-1963, Photographer Kazukaitis, PHC, USN; Subject: RADM [Rear Admiral] James R. Reedy, USN, Commander of OPERATION DEEPFREEZE and Lowell Thomas, CBS News Correspondent hold a press conference with the New Zealand press media in Christchurch after completing an unprecedented non-stop flight from Capetown, South Africa to McMurdo Sound Antarctica, terminating at Harewood International Airport, Christchurch New Zealand. RADM Reedy attended the World Conference of the Scientific Committee of Antarctica Research (SCAR) held in Capetown, South Africa, 6-verso
    - Date 12-15-1964, Photographer Regina; Scenic view of the edge of the glacier that flows off of Mt. Erebus into Erebus Bay, McMurdo Sound, Antarctica, 7
    - Verso: Date 12-15-1964, Photographer Regina; Scenic view of the edge of the glacier that flows off of Mt. Erebus into Erebus Bay, McMurdo Sound, Antarctica, 7-verso
    - Date 12-31-1965, Photographer A. W. Thomas; USS Burton Island, USS Atka, and the USS Glacier push together to move hugh iceberg from channel of broken ice leading to McMurdo Station, Antarctica, 8
    - Verso: Date 12-31-1965, Photographer A. W. Thomas; USS Burton Island, USS Atka, and the USS Glacier push together to move hugh iceberg from channel of broken ice leading to McMurdo Station, Antarctica, 8-verso
  - Subject files: Antarctica [includes color photographs], undated; 18 (Box 1537)
    - Rear Admiral James Reedy and L.T. [2 copies], 1
    - Verso: Rear Admiral James Reedy and L.T., 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and man standing in front of Navy rescue plane], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas with the United States Navy], 3
    - [Airplane in front of sunset], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas in front of a mountain of snow], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and an unidentified man], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas petting a dog], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas surrounded by penguins], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas and another man sleeping in a plane], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas and three members of the United States Navy], 11
    - [Penguin standing over its eggs], 12
    - Emperor and chicks, 13
    - Verso: Emperor and chicks, 13-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas at Scott Base], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to a seal], 15
    - [Unidentified man walking across the snow], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas and three other men], 17
    - [Iceberg], 18
    - Verso: Coast Guard Icebreakers Aid Navy Task Group In Arctic Mission Icebergs assume fantastic shapes after they break from mother glacier [continued], 18-verso
  - Subject files: Antarctica (the Lowell Thomas Mountains), 1965; 19 (Box 1537)
    - L.T. mtn [mountain] camp, 25 December 1965, 1
    - Verso: L.T. mtn [mountain] camp, 25 December 1965, 1-verso
  - Subject files: Gene Anthony [color photographs], undated; 20 (Box 1537)
    - Artist - Gene Anthony [portrait of Lowell Thomas], 1
    - Verso: Artist - Gene Anthony [portrait of Lowell Thomas], 1-verso
    - J. Reuben Clark; Gene & Ellen Anthony Portrait Painting, 320 Laguna Terrace, Simi, California [portrait of J.Reuben Clark], 2
    - Verso: J. Reuben Clark; Gene & Ellen Anthony Portrait Painting, 320 Laguna Terrace, Simi, California [portrait of J.Reuben Clark], 2-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas and Gene Anthony holding a portrait], 3
    - [Portrait of a woman done by Gene Anthony], 4
  - Subject files: Harold W. Arlin and Lowell Thomas, circa 1924; 21 (Box 1537)
    - Harold Arlin and L. T. He may have been the first regular radio announcer, at any rate, he put LT on the air in March 1925 for the latter's first broadcast - telling the story of Man's First Flight Around the World, 1
    - Verso: Harold Arlin and L. T. He may have been the first regular radio announcer, at any rate, he put LT on the air in March 1925 for the latter's first broadcast - telling the story of Man's First Flight Around the World, 1-verso
    - Note: [letter from Westinghouse Electric Corporation] Dear Lowell: Here is the picture of you and Harold Arlin at the Westinghouse "Home of Tomarrow" here in Mansfield. The delay in getting it to you was the result of borrowing Harold's copy and having it copied in our photographic department. A couple of notes -- the "Home of Tomorrow" was dedicated on February 21, 1934 -- your broadcast was on March 15, 1934. Hope you find the picture pleasurable. Sincerely, [signed] J. Gilbert Baird, 2
  - Subject files: Army-Navy Legion of Valor Annual Dinner, 1933 April 6; 22 (Box 1537)
    - Caption: Annual Dinner; Army-Navy Legion of Valor; Hotel Victoria - N.Y. - Apr. 6 - 1933s, 1
  Box 1538
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: General Henry H. "Hap" Arnold and Lowell Thomas, 1927; 1 (Box 1538)
    - Caption: H. H. Arnold [autograph]; Ft. Riley, Kan [Fort Riley, Kansas], Nov. 28, 1927 Verso: Gen "Hap" Arnold and LT and ? [left to right: General Arnold in flight gear, Lowell Thomas in flight gear, unidentified officer], 1
    - Gen. "Hap" Arnold + L.T. + ? [6 copies], 2
    - Verso: Gen. "Hap" Arnold + L.T. + ?, 2-verso
    - Lowell center in 1930 General Arnold left-, 3
    - Verso: Lowell center in 1930 General Arnold left-, 3-verso
    - [L.T. and General "Hap" Arnold], 4
    - Lowell Thomas as he looked on his 25,000-mile airplane journey over Europe [Lowell Thomas wearing flight gear] [6 copies], 5
    - Note: Lowell Thomas as he looked on his 25,000-mile airplane journey over Europe [Lowell Thomas wearing flight gear], 6
  - Subject files: Around the world special passenger flight (Pan American World Airways), 1947; 2 (Box 1538)
    - Note: LT launching the first passenger flight around the world. Directly behind him are Juan Trippe, publishers Frank Gannett, Gardner Cowles and Roy Howard. On the left is Edwin D. Canham, publisher of the Christian Science Monitor; behind him is Maurice T. Moore, chairman of the board of Time, Inc; and at top Barry Faris of INS. (Electra [Electra Nicks?] on steps) and to her right James Stahlman, publisher of the Nashville Banner, 1
    - Note: Call PAN AMERICAN - Photographic Dept. Many years ago, in the thirties, Mr. Thomas helped you folks at Pan Am to launch the first passenger fligt around the world, from LaGuardia. It might have been in the forties. Juan Trippe, Roy Howard, Stallman, were there. L.T. did a b.c from the steps of the plane and Mr. Trippe was in the picture at Mr, T's side. L.T. wants one or two or three or 4, in which Trippe is in the center and can be seen slearly. Let him have a few to make a choice., 2
    - Note: #1 - Maurice T. Moore Chairman Bd. Of Time, Inc. (behind [?]) #2 Erwin D. Canham, Publisher, Christian Science Monitor. ([?]), 3
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking in front of a plane at Pan American World Airways], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas doing an NBC broadcast in front of a plane at Pan American World Airways], 5
    - [Group of people getting off a plane at Pan American World Airways], 6
  - Subject files: Mt. Assiniboine, Canada (photography by Ray H. Coulter), 1967; 3 (Box 1538)
    - Strom's halfway, #1 "Strom's Halfway", 1
    - Verso: Strom's halfway, #1 "Strom's Halfway", 1-verso
    - # 2 Assiniboine Lodge 1967, 2
    - Verso: # 2 Assiniboine Lodge 1967, 2-verso
    - 3. "Parting", 3
    - Verso: 3. "Parting", 3-verso
    - Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas leaving Assiniboine 1967, #6 Take-Off, 4
    - Verso: Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas leaving Assiniboine 1967, #6 Take-Off, 4-verso
    - Ann Lou Coulter, #10 Rest-stop, Assiniboine Country, 5
    - Verso: Ann Lou Coulter, #10 Rest-stop, Assiniboine Country, 5-verso
    - Elizabeth Rummel, Bridget Jones, Assiniboine Lodge 1967, #11 "Lizzie and Bridget", 6
    - Verso: Elizabeth Rummel, Bridget Jones, Assiniboine Lodge 1967, #11 "Lizzie and Bridget", 6-verso
    - Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas, # 12 "Happy Land", 7
    - Verso: Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas, # 12 "Happy Land", 7-verso
    - Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas, # 12 "Happy Land", 8
    - Verso: Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas, # 12 "Happy Land", 8-verso
    - Al Johnston #13 "Master of His Trade", 9
    - Verso: Al Johnston #13 "Master of His Trade", 9-verso
    - Al Johnston of Banff Alta. [Alberta], "Al" is one of the greatest guides in the business. A real "pro", #14 "Assiniboine Al", 10
    - Verso: Al Johnston of Banff Alta. [Alberta], "Al" is one of the greatest guides in the business. A real "pro", #14 "Assiniboine Al", 10-verso
    - Erling Strom leading the Coulter party over Allenby Pass 1967, #15 "Over the Top.", 11
    - Verso: Erling Strom leading the Coulter party over Allenby Pass 1967, #15 "Over the Top.", 11-verso
    - Lowell Thomas. Mrs. Thomas, Erling Strom 1967, # 16 "Reunion" at Assiniboine, 12
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas. Mrs. Thomas, Erling Strom 1967, # 16 "Reunion" at Assiniboine, 12-verso
    - Lowell Thomas. Mrs. Thomas, Erling Strom 1967, # 16 "Reunion" at Assiniboine, 13
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas. Mrs. Thomas, Erling Strom 1967, # 16 "Reunion" at Assiniboine, 13-verso
    - Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas at Assiniboine, #17 " It's a different world", 14
    - Verso: Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas at Assiniboine, #17 " It's a different world", 14-verso
    - Mr. Lowell Thomas, ready for more adventure, # 18 "Saddled Up.", 15
    - Verso: Mr. Lowell Thomas, ready for more adventure, # 18 "Saddled Up.", 15-verso
    - Ann Lou Coulter in # 19 "Adventure Land", 16
    - Verso: Ann Lou Coulter in # 19 "Adventure Land", 16-verso
    - First View of Assiniboine from Og Pass, Ann Lou Coulter and Guide not to mention the Matterhorn of the Rockies, Mt. Assiniboine, #20 Tomorrow's Adventure, 17
    - Verso: First View of Assiniboine from Og Pass, Ann Lou Coulter and Guide not to mention the Matterhorn of the Rockies, Mt. Assiniboine, #20 Tomorrow's Adventure, 17-verso
    - Mt. Assiniboine from #21 Sunburst Camp, 18
    - Verso: Mt. Assiniboine from #21 Sunburst Camp, 18-verso
    - Elizabeth Rummel's Cabin on Sunburst Lake., #22 Sunburst Camp, 19
    - Verso: Elizabeth Rummel's Cabin on Sunburst Lake., #22 Sunburst Camp, 19-verso
    - "Tommy" [Lowell Thomas] Erling [Strom] and Assiniboine, # 23 "Titans Three", 20
    - Verso: "Tommy" [Lowell Thomas] Erling [Strom] and Assiniboine, # 23 "Titans Three", 20-verso
    - "Tommy" [Lowell Thomas] Erling [Strom] and Assiniboine, # 23 "Titans Three", 21
    - Verso: "Tommy" [Lowell Thomas] Erling [Strom] and Assiniboine, # 23 "Titans Three", 21-verso
    - Thomas's lift off, # 24 "Dragonfly", 22
    - Verso: Thomas's lift off, # 24 "Dragonfly", 22-verso
    - Thomas's lift off, # 24 "Dragonfly", 23
    - Verso: Thomas's lift off, # 24 "Dragonfly", 23-verso
    - Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas, # 25 "Tommy and Mate", 24
    - Verso: Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas, # 25 "Tommy and Mate", 24-verso
    - Lowell Thomas Sr., #27 "Lets Go", 25
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas Sr., #27 "Lets Go", 25-verso
    - Mr. Lowell Thomas Sr., 28 "Mounted", 26
    - Verso: Mr. Lowell Thomas Sr., 28 "Mounted", 26-verso
    - Siri, Alice Powell and "Tommy" [Lowell Thomas's, 29 "Discussion"], 27
    - Verso: Siri, Alice Powell and "Tommy" [Lowell Thomas's, 29 "Discussion"], 27-verso
    - Mount Assiniboine, The Matterhorn of the Canadian Rockies, #30 "Cool, Man, Cool", 28
    - Verso: Mount Assiniboine, The Matterhorn of the Canadian Rockies, #30 "Cool, Man, Cool", 28-verso
  - Subject files: Astronauts and Lowell Thomas, undated; 4 (Box 1538)
    - For LT's office and Garst Museum; Astronauts, one is Grissom [Gus Grissom, second from right], 1
    - Verso: For LT's office and Garst Museum; Astronauts, one is Grissom [Gus Grissom, second from right], 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with an unidentified man], 2
  - Subject files: Australia landscapes, undated; 5 (Box 1538)
    - [Two men sitting on waterfront at a park in Australia], 1
    - [Distant city in Australia], 2
    - [Lily pads in a lake in Australia], 3
    - [Lily pads with blossoms in Australia], 4
    - [Trees in Australia], 5
    - [Hydrangeas in Australia], 6
  - Subject files: Aviation [includes one color photograph], 1929 - circa 1960s; 6 (Box 1538)
    - Cliff Henderson and some local boys @ Cleveland [?] 1929, 1
    - Verso: Cliff Henderson and some local boys @ Cleveland [?] 1929, 1-verso
    - At Elgin Air Force Base, Nov. 1+2, 1956, 2